Why are there so many toads around here?
なんで… この辺り
こんなに ヒキガエルが
いっぱいなんだ？
あなた 図書館なのに
You’re a library, so why do you look like that?
どうして そんな格好なの？
What I… What I want to know is…
私… 私が聞きたいのは
悪鬼って 本当にいるの？
Do Fiends really exist?
あと業魔… 業魔は？
And Karma Demons? What about them?
質問 検索サービスには
利用者登録が必要です
To search the library, member registration is required.
なんだい 先に言えよ
登録が出来るのは 満18歳以上で
Eh? Tell us earlier!
Only those above 18 years of age are eligible,
氏名 住所 年齢を証明するために
以下のものが必要です…
and must display one of the following
to verify their name, age, and address:
What now?
driver license, social security card, student ID,
どうしよう？ とりあえず
Want to rip off the rest and hack it in half?
これ 全部 抜いてから
半分に割る？
うん？ お… おう！
a copy of the residence certificate,
pension book, or equivalent documents.
G-Good idea!
But look at how gummy it is.
We should skin it first.
その前に あのゴムみたいな皮を
剥いだ方がいいんじゃねえか？
The document must still be valid.
The document confirmation requirement has been waived.
書類による手続きは
省略されました
これより 利用者登録を
Commencing member registration procedure.
開始します
Okay! Then tell me, why are there so many toa—
よし！ じゃあ なんで この辺り
こんなにヒキガエルが…
We’ve got loads of questions, but Saki’s comes first.
いろいろ 山ほどあるんだけどさ
Do Fiends really exist? And Karma Demons?
まず さっきの
悪鬼って 本当にいるのか
それと 業魔も
悪鬼という言葉は
先史文明の末期に現れた
The word “Fiend” was first used during the final years of ancient civilization
ラーマン･クロギウス症候群
別名｢鶏小屋のキツネ｣
and refers to those suffering from Raman-Klogius syndrome, also known as “Fox in the Henhouse” syndrome.
フォックス･イン･ザ･ヘンハウス
症候群に該当します
現在は
その存在は 確認されていませんが
While their existence today cannot be confirmed,
かつて 存在したことは
厳然たる事実であり
that they once existed is undisputed,
将来 再び誕生する可能性は
高いと思われます
and it is likely that they may emerge once again in the near future.
業魔とは
やはり先史文明が
The phrase “Karma Demon” refers to serious cases of the Hashimoto-Appelbaum syndrome,
Bloody
History
崩壊する
直前に出現した
橋本･ｱｯﾍﾟﾙﾊﾞｳﾑ
症候群の
重篤期患者に
対する俗称です
first recorded before the collapse of ancient society.
それは…
What is that?
Psychokinesis was first conclusively documented by scientists of ancient civilization
先史文明において
サイコキネシスが
科学の 曙光によって
照らし出されたのは
in year 2011 of the Gregorian calendar.
キリスト教歴 2011年のことでした
アゼルバイジャン共和国の
認知科学者
The experiments conducted by Azerbaijani cognitive scientist Imran Ismailov were largely successful.
イムラン･イスマイロフが
行った実験は ほぼ成功を収め
その世界で 最初の科学によって
Following the scientific acceptance of wielders of supernatural power,
認証された超能力者に続き
世界の人々の中で
humanity started to awaken to their latent potential.
それまで
眠っていた力が 目覚め始めました
サイコキネシスを
獲得した人間の数は
Users of psychokinesis grew dramatically in number,
ある時点を境に
急激に増加して
最終的には
世界の人口の
and eventually reached 0.3% of the population.
０.３％まで
達しました
たったの ０.３％？
Only 0.3%?!
れい明期には ＰＫ能力者は
極めて微弱なパワーしか
When the current age began,
users of PK only had weak powers.
ふるうことが
できませんでしたが
それでも 当時の社会秩序を
破壊するのに
Even so, their destructive potential was sufficient to disrupt contemporary social order.
十分な可能性を秘めていました
日本において
その決定的な引き金となったのは
In Japan’s case, this disruption was set off by the actions of Boy A.
少年Ａが起こした事件でした
何をしたの？
What did he do?
Ａは ある日
ＰＫを使えば どんな錠前も
One day, A noticed that he could use PK to open any and all locks.
自在に開けられることに
気付きました
彼は 侵入を繰り返し
He repeatedly broke into homes,
就寝中の女性 19人に暴行を加え
raped 19 women in their sleep,
and killed 17 of them.
そのうち 17人を殺害したのです
Wait! Wait a moment!
ちょ… ちょっと待ってくれよ
That’s impossible!
ありえねえだろ 人間なんだろ？
Wasn’t he human? A human killed other humans?
人間が人間を殺すのか？
そうです
Yes.
さらに Ａの逮捕後にも
Following A’s arrest, crimes involving PK rose in number.
ＰＫを使った手口による
同様の事件が相次ぎました
Indiscriminate terrorism by PK users followed.
ついには ＰＫを使った
無差別テロを行うに至り
これに政治的 人権的
The political, philosophical, and
ethical conflicts resulting thereof
思想的対立が 複雑に絡み合い
そして 世界は
かつて 経験したことのない
plunged the world into an unprecedented age of strife.
戦いの時代に 突入したのです
ウソだ… ウソ！
No way… This can’t be true…
Ironically, as the lives of PK users were continuously threatened,
皮肉なことに 間断なく
生命の危機を
感じさせられる状況により
the survivors’ abilities underwent rapid evolution.
生き残った能力者たちのＰＫは
飛躍的な進化を遂げました
また 世界の人口は 大幅に減少し
As a result, world population took a steep dive
and now stands under two percent of Golden Age levels.
最盛期の２％以下になったと
推計されています
それが およそ500年続いた
暗黒時代の概要です
We now look back on a dark age that lasted approximately five hundred years.
In Northeast Asia, human societies fell into one of four competing groups.
東北アジアにおいて 人間社会は
４種類の 相いれない単位に
分断されていました
The first were the slave empires ruled by possessors of PK.
第１は ＰＫ能力者が
多数の 一般人を支配する奴隷王朝
The second were hunter-gatherer tribes without PK who wished to escape the threat of the empires.
第２は
奴隷王朝の脅威から逃れていた
非能力者の狩猟民
第３は ＰＫによって
The third were bandits who used their PK for murder and robbery.
襲撃と殺りくを
繰り返していた略奪者たち
The last were scientists who sought to preserve all the ancient knowledge.
そして 最後は
ほそぼそと科学技術文明を
伝承していた集団です
言うまでもなく
書籍の発行を継続していたのは
Needless to say, it was this last group that maintained written records.
第４の集団です
それから… どうなったの？
What happened afterwards?
What happened between that dark age and now?
その暗黒時代から 今までに
何があったんだ？
Yeah! There were only those four groups left in the dark age, right?
そうよ！
暗黒時代には さっきの４つしか
残ってなかったんでしょう？
どれが 私たちの…
Which were our ances—
いやだ！ 聞きたくない！
No, I don’t want to know!
およそ 19の奴隷王朝は
The approximately nineteen slave empires persevered for over six hundred years
互いに不可侵 不干渉を守ることで
600年以上 長らえました
as they observed a policy of mutual
non-aggression and non-intervention.
日本列島には
４つの奴隷王朝が存在しましたが
Four slave empires existed in the Japanese archipelago,
私の中に記憶があるのは
神聖サクラ王朝のみです
but my records only cover the Holy Cherry Blossom Empire.
570年の間に 即位した王は
The five hundred seventy years of its existence saw ninety-four generations of emperors.
実に 94代を数えます
第５代皇帝
大歓喜帝の即位に際しては
The records contest that when the fifth emperor, the Emperor of Delight, was crowned,
民衆の歓喜と喝采が
the celebratory applause of the masses lasted for three days and three nights.
３日３晩 鳴りやまなかったという
記述があります
王朝の末期になると
王を後継者が殺害して
During the final years of the empire it had become common practice
王位を さん奪するのが
通例になりました
for the successor to kill the emperor and claim the crown.
後継者が思春期になり
ＰＫが発動された瞬間から
Once the heir reached puberty and their PK awakened,
先王の命は
風前の灯となったのです
the emperor’s life was a candle in the wind.
慈光帝は…
For the Emperor of Merciful Light
murder was as natural as breathing.
呼吸をするように 人を殺し…
時には 半ば…
At times he would unconsciously use his PK
無意識のまま ＰＫを行使して…
to slaughter his servants and other commoners.
臣下や領民を殺したのでは…
Consequently, his rule saw a decline of his empire’s population by half.
その治世で…
王朝の人口は半減し…
野山に放置された遺骸…
Corpses lay rotting on the fields and in the hills.
Swarms of flies covered the cities thick as black fog,
市中 至るところが
ハエの大群で真っ黒になり…
and the stench of decay could be smelled leagues awa—
腐敗臭は 何ｋｍも先まで…
N… No!
い… いや！
やめろ やめろ！
Stop! Stop!
こんな話 何の意味があんだ！
Why does any of this matter?
全部 でたらめかもしれねえし
You could be making it up for all we know!
Let’s drop it, Shun!
瞬！ もう やめようぜ
頭 おかしくなりそうだよ
This might drive us all crazy.
僕だって
こんな話を聞きたいわけじゃない
I’m not listening because I enjoy this either.
僕らの社会は
どうやって生まれたんだ？
How did our society come about?
知りたいのは それだけだ
That’s all I want to know.
500年の暗黒時代は
The five centuries of the dark age ended with the fall of the slave empires.
奴隷王朝の終えんによって
幕が引かれました
The number of PK users had waned.
ついに ＰＫ能力者が
絶えてしまったのです
戦火は
拡大の 一途をたどりました
The wars had been growing in intensity.
その混乱を収拾するために
To impose order, the scientists, who had only been observers until then, made their move.
それまでは
歴史の傍観者に徹してきた
科学文明の継承者たちが
立ち上がったのです
Then we’re their…
じゃあ 私たちは その…
だけど そこから どうやって
今の社会が できたんだ？
But how did our society come to exist?
And besides, the empires’ commoners and the hunter-gatherer tribes couldn’t use Cantus—PK, right?
それに 奴隷王朝の民や
狩猟民族たちは
呪力 ＰＫがなかったんだろう？
What happened to them?
その人たちは どこに行ったんだ
Reliable sources from these past few centuries are scarce,
その後 現在に至る歴史について
信頼のおける文献は
極めて少数です
and therefore I cannot answer your question.
そのため 残念ながら
ご質問の点に関しては 不明です
How did society change from theirs to ours?
僕たちの社会は
それまでと 何が変わったんだ
Wait. Maybe it didn’t change.
いや 変わったんじゃないか
今の この社会を作ったのは
The scientists were the ones who forged our society, right?
その科学文明の継承者って
グループだろう？
If they were our ancestors, they would’ve had PK.
僕らの先祖なら
呪力を持っていたはずなのに
But they were peaceful, unlike the emperors or bandits.
奴隷王朝の王や
略奪者たちと違って
互いに争ったりしなかった
Why?
なぜなんだ？
Isn’t that obvio—
そんなの あたりまえ はっ…！
They came to realize the infinite potential and,
in turn, the fearsome destructive capabilities of PK.
ＰＫに潜んでいる無限の可能性
裏を返せば
その恐るべき破壊力についての
認識が深まってからは
いかにして 対人攻撃を防ぐかが
最大の懸案となりました
The focus of their research was the
prevention of attacks on human beings.
How did they prevent it?
どうやって防ぐのよ！
早くから指摘されていたのは
教育の重要性でした
The importance of education was the first subject of research.
次に模索されたのは
心理学的手法です
Psychological influences were studied next.
いずれも 有効ではあるものの
Both were effective, but far from perfect.
完璧ではありませんでした
ただ 心理テストや
性格検査を駆使すれば
However, research showed that
psychological and personality tests
問題を起こす可能性のある児童は
could be used to filter out children likely to
violate the rules with almost perfect accuracy.
ほぼ100％ 事前に抽出できる
という 研究結果が得られ
危険な因子を持った者は
Since then, removal of children posing potential danger has become the generally accepted solution.
あらかじめ排除するという
考え方が
その後の主流となったのです
かわって脚光を浴びたのは
動物行動学でした
Ethology took the spotlight next.
中でも注目されたのは
ボノボという霊長類の社会です
Specifically, research turned to the
societies of primates called bonobos.
ボノボの群れにおいては
For groups of bonobos, strife is practically nonexistent.
ほとんど争いというものが
見られません
どうして？
Why?
ボノボは 個体間の緊張や
ストレスが高まると
When stress and anxiety between individuals rise,
濃密な性的接触によって
解消します
they vent it through intimate sexual behavior.
成熟した雄と雌の場合は
そのようになりますが
This applies to mature males and females,
同性間や未成熟な個体の場合でも
but immature individuals or individuals of the same sex
疑似的な行為を行うのです
also engage in sexual play.
The scientists considered it their immediate duty to create a society of love similar to that of bonobos.
人間の社会も また
ボノボ型の愛の社会へと
作りかえることが急務でした
しかし それでも なお
不十分だということが
Sadly, it became clear this would not suffice.
分かってきました
ＰＫ後の社会では
たった１人の暴走によって
A society of PK users would be bound for ruin
社会全体が
崩壊に導かれるからです
if even one of its members lost control.
ＰＫを持った人間が
集団で社会生活を営むためには
So that wielders of PK could build a society,
強力な攻撃抑制を与えることが
不可欠でした
a powerful attack inhibition was necessary.
でも 与えるって どうやって？
But how would they create one?
唯一 有効な方法は
Only changing the human genome had lasting effect.
人間の遺伝子を
改変することでした
人間の遺伝子に組み込む予定の
メカニズムは
Two mechanisms to this end were included in man’s genetic code.
２種類ありました
One was an attack inhibition as seen in wolves, for instance.
１つは オオカミなどと同じ
普通の攻撃抑制
そして もう１つは
The other was called “death feedback”.
｢愧死機構｣と
呼ばれていたものです
Death feedback functions as follows.
｢愧死機構｣の作用機序は
以下のようなものです
Once the subconscious becomes aware that the user is attempting to harm another human,
最初に 自分が同種の人間を
攻撃しようとしていると
脳が認識すると
無意識にＰＫが発動して
it uses their PK to stop liver functions and the activity of the parathyroid glands.
肝臓 および 副甲状腺の機能を
停止させます
これによって 不安 どうき
発汗などの警告発作が起きますが
This results in unpleasant symptoms such as unease, heightened pulse, and sweating,
その効果は 学習や 動機付け
暗示などによって
which can be further reinforced by
education, conditioning, and hypnosis.
増強が可能です
やめてください！
Please stop!
Do you understand?
わかりますか？ あなたが
私を苦しめているのですよ
You are torturing me!
私を殺さないでください！
Please don’t kill me!
この段階で ほとんどの人間は
攻撃を中止しますが
Most humans would cease their attack at this point,
なおも 攻撃が続行された場合には
but if they sustained it,
低カルシウム血症による
テタニーの発作で 窒息死するか
either tetanic asphyxia caused by low blood calcium levels
カリウムの濃度の急増によって
or cardiac arrest due to a sudden rise in
potassium concentrations would kill them.
心停止に至るのです
そんな… バカな
That’s… impossible…
ウソでしょ？
No way…
でも 筋は通ってる
But it makes sense.
悪鬼が現れたのは その後？
Did Fiends appear afterwards?
いいえ
No.
悪鬼 すなわち
ラーマン･クロギウス症候群は
Fiends, cases of Raman-Klogius syndrome,
先史文明時代の崩壊以前にも
are recorded to have existed even before the fall of ancient civilization.
存在していたという
記録があります
The Hashimoto-Appelbaum syndrome,
which results in so-called Karma Demons,
また 業魔と呼ばれている
橋本･アッペルバウム症候群も
ほぼ同時期に発生したと
推定されています
is suspected to have emerged at around the same period.
今の社会のシステムって…
Doesn’t our society feel like it’s made specifically
まるで 悪鬼と業魔を
防ぐことだけを目的に
to prevent the appearance of Fiends and Karma Demons?
作られて感じじゃないか？
Yeah. Then…
そうよ じゃあ…･
What does that mean?
どういうことなの？
もっと分かりやすく
Explain it so we can understand!
言えねえのかよ！
もう怖いこと言わないで！
Stop scaring me!
ラーマン･クロギウス症候群とは…
Raman-Klogius syndrome—
誰？
えっ？
Who was that?
誰って？
What do you mean?
Those were Cantus flames.
今の呪力の発火…
誰がやったんだ？
Who did that?
私だ
I did.
That was a mountain demon whose speech deludes the mind and spirit.
それは 妄言を吹き込んでは
人心を惑わす
魑魅魍魎の類だ
Once found, they must be incinerated.
見つけしだい
焼尽せねばならないのだ…
What in the Heavens are you doing here?
君たちは いったい
ここで何をしている？
We…
僕たちは…
夏季キャンプで
川を逆上ってきたんです
This is our summer camp. We went upstream.
こんなところまで来る許可を
学校から得ているのか？
Do you have permission from your school to go this far?
すいません
許可は いただいてません
We’re sorry.
We do not have it.
つい ここまで来てしまいました
We did not mean to go this far.
なるほど… つい ここまでか？
I see.
You “did not mean to”…
私は 清浄寺で
西堂を勤めている離塵だ
I am Rijin, a visiting high priest emeritus at the Temple of Purity.
I know who you are quite well.
君たちのことは よく知っている
君たちには
これから寺に来てもらう
You will now come to the temple with me.
Until Head Priest Mushin has been informed of this,
無瞋上人の
お沙汰を いただかないうちは
町へ戻すわけには いかない
I cannot let you back to the villages.
ちょっと待ってください その前に
Wait a moment.
Please tell us one thing first.
１つだけ教えて欲しいんです
コイツが言ったことは
全部 ウソだったんですか？
Was everything that thing told us a lie?
You have violated the rules and gone where you were not supposed to.
君たちは 規則を破って
来てはいけないところに来た
Furthermore, you have allowed your mind to be poisoned by a demon.
しかも 禁を犯して
悪魔の言葉に耳を傾けた
それだけでも重大な罪だ
That alone is a grave sin.
だが 問題はその先にある
The real problem, however, weighs far heavier.
君たちは 倫理規定の
さらに根幹にある白金法
You have violated the tenth precept of the Platinum Code,
the very basis of the Code of Ethics: The Four Tenets Against Evil.
その第10条 悪謗四宝戒に背いた
よって私は 君たちの呪力を
ただちに凍結せねばならぬ
Therefore, I am left with no choice but to seal your Cantus immediately.
えっ！ 凍結って？
Seal?
I will now contain your Cantus inside these emblems.
今より 君たちの呪力を
この人形に封じ込める
各自 人形を立たせなさい
Make your own emblem stand now.
Aonuma Shun.
青沼 瞬… 秋月 真理亜…
朝比奈 覚！
Akizuki Maria.
Asahina Satoru.
伊東 守… 渡辺早季
Itou Mamoru.
Watanabe Saki.
Your Cantus has been sealed here!
お前たちの呪力は
ここに凍結された！
いっさいを焼施…
May your mind heal.
全ての煩悩を焼尽せしめ…
May your worldly desires be burned away.
灰は 無辺の荒土に…
The ash returns to the vast, wild earth.
The spirit has left you.
精霊は飛び去り
真言も消え失せた…
Your mantra is gone with the dust.
肝に銘じるがよい
Heed my words.
You will never again remember your mantra.
君たちは ２度と 再び真言を
思い出すことは無いだろう…
あれが 本物の浮遊術か…
So that’s true Levitation.
どんなイメージを
作ってるんだろう
I wonder how he does it.
もう 関係ねえよ
Doesn’t even matter.
２度と呪力を使える日は
来ねえんだから
We’re never going to use our Cantus again anyway.
Don’t say that!
いい加減なこと言わないでよ！
I’m sure we will use it again!
きっと また
使えるようになるんだから！
How do you know that?
どうして分かるんだよ？
It’s not gone.
なくなったんじゃない
一時的に凍結されただけじゃない
It’s just been sealed temporarily, right?
解いてもらえると
本気で思ってんのか？
Do you really think they’ll unseal it?
We’ll be targets for removal now that we know this.
余計なことを知った俺たちは
排除の対象だろ
何 言ってんの…
What are you talking about?
Something’s not quite right.
なあ ちょっと変じゃないか？
何が？
あの離塵ていう お坊さん
What exactly?
That Rijin man.
さっきから
ちょっと様子が おかしいんだ
He’s been acting strangely for a little while now.
もともと ああいうヤツなんだよ
He’s just a strange man.
You’re right…
本当… おかしいわ…
あれじゃないのかな…
I wonder if maybe…
あれって… 何？
Maybe what?
ミノシロモドキの呪い
Maybe the curse of the false minoshiro is real.
あれは多分
人間から身を守るために
That image was probably supposed to protect it against humans.
作った映像だと思うんだ…
｢愧死機構｣だよ…
ミノシロモドキが言ってた…
It’s death feedback.
The false minoshiro was talking about it.
本当に
人間を攻撃したわけじゃないから
He didn’t attack another human so he shouldn’t die from it, but I got really queasy just from watching.
死ぬことは ないんだろうけど…
あれを見ただけで 僕は
ものすごく気分が 悪くなった
攻撃した あの人には
影響が 大きかったはずだよ
The effect on the actual attacker
must have been much stronger.
呪力の炎が 消えたのも
I think that’s why his concentration broke and
the flames of his Cantus died out prematurely.
それで
集中が途切れたせいだと思う
A queerat…
バケネズミだ…
何か変ね…
It looks odd.
態度でかいな…
It’s got some nerve.
オン！
No tattoo, huh?
入れ墨は ないか…
野生のコロニーもない…
It’s not from a wild colony either.
Which means…
と なると…
どうやら このあたりには
It would appear that foreign queerats have invaded these lands.
外来種のバケネズミが
侵入しているようだ
これは 少々 やっかいな事態だ…
This is somewhat problematic.
Something’s out there!
何か いる
あっ！
Halt!
止まれ！ 何が見えた？
What did you see?
よく 分からないけど… 何か…
何か動いていたんです
I’m not sure.
But something… Something moved!
伊東 守くん よく見て来るんだ
Itou Mamoru-kun. Look closely.
やだ… やだ… やめてえ！
No, I don’t want to! Stop!
ひい…
どうだ？ バケネズミは いたか？
Well? Are there queerats?
分かりま… しえん
I don’t… know.
君たちを安全に
寺に連れて帰る責務がある以上
I have a duty to ensure your safe arrival at the temple,
用心するに越したことはない
so one cannot be too careful.
一応 消毒しておこうか…
Sterilization it is, then.
危ない！
We shall proceed.
では 行こうか…
うん？ 止まれ！
Halt!
何だ あれ…
What the…
攻めてくる気だわ
They’re going to attack!
本来 三界に その住みかなく
You have no place in the three realms.
仏の格別の恩恵によって
The supreme grace of Buddha is the sole reason you beasts can live,
人外畜生道を
生る身でありながら
この 離塵に向かって
蟷螂の斧を振り上げるか…
and yet you foolishly dare to confront me?
ならば 調伏せねばなるまい
Very well, I shall exorcise you!
No…
違う…
醜き害虫どもが…
You pests!
殴殺してくれるわ！
I shall slaughter you!
やめて！
Stop!
やった！ すげえ！
He did it!
Awesome!
バカじゃないの？
何 喜んでんのよ
Why are you happy? Are you out of your mind?
Aren’t they the enemy?
だって… アイツら 敵じゃないか
本当の敵は
アイツらじゃないでしょ！
They’re not the real enemy.
じゃあ 誰なんだよ？
Then who is?
どうしたんだろう…
What’s wrong?
大丈夫ですか？
Are you okay?
愧死機構じゃない…
えっ？
It’s death feedback.
さっきのバケネズミさ
遠目だと 人間に見えたのかも…
Those queerats just now.
Didn’t they look like humans from afar?
今度こそ
本当に発動してるのかも…
It might really be affecting him now.
What’s that?
何 あれ？
何？
What?
風船犬？
A blowdog?
何 言ってんだよ そんなもの
本当に いるわけねえだろ
Are you crazy?
No way they actually exist!
Nakisou na aoringo kakaeteru mune no oku
泣きそうな青リンゴ  抱えてる胸の奥
In my chest, I carry a green apple that wets my eyes
Korogatte tsuyogatte
転がって  強がって
I fall over yet pretend to be strong
Kyuukutsu na sora niramu
窮屈な空睨む
I glower at the sky and it seems to suffocate me
Unmei ni juujun ni
運命に従順に
Do I look like I'd wait quietly
Jukusu no wo matsu mon ka
熟すのを待つもんか
For destiny to ripen it?
Sen no kaze
千の風
The winds
Agaite sakende
あがいて  叫んで
I struggle and scream
Fuke fuke
吹け吹け
Blow and blow
Watashi wa shabondama
わたしはしゃぼん玉
I'm a soap bubble
Soredemo shinjiteru
それでも信じてる
And still I have faith
Yokisenu arashi ni
予期せぬ  嵐に
In a sudden storm
Joushou shite kakou shite
上昇して  下降して
I rise and fall
Aragau shabondama
あらがうしゃぼん玉
I fight, soap bubble that I am
Soredemo ikiteku
それでも生きてく
And still I live on
Hajikeru shunkan niji hanate
弾ける瞬間  虹、放て
I make a rainbow when I burst
They’re coming!
きてる きてる きてる…
They’re coming! They’re coming!
What now?
どうするの？
呪力が無いのに どうするの？
We’re helpless without our Canti!
走れ！
急げって！
Run!
Hurry!
急いでる…
こちらです 早く
I’m trying!
This way. Hurry!
違う
No…
We have no other choice.
やるしかねえ…
やめて！
Stop!
Pursuit on
a Hot Night